Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries
No living being was harmed during the
filming of this series.
Episode 108
"One day later"
No one was hurt, right, Hatuns?
The stone you are not afraid
of may harm you, my Bey.
Alçiçek has an aide, my Bey.
I locked the door on Bengi.
So, we went out quietly and came.
I swear Bengi Hatun was so angry.
Alçiçek's aide is a good girl.
What about you, my Bey?
How did you get out of
all those spears?
When we told them we had put
gunpowder around the castle...
They had to leave us.
No, does this make sense?
It's ours, I ask Allah's forgiveness
But the suspicion was
enough, was it not, my Bey?
They must have understood
the truth after we left.
However, Bengi will do something.
So, we will take our
precautions accordingly.
Take precautions.
We are as promised about the wedding....
We're going to get İnegöl.
And we will have our
wedding in İnegöl, Inshallah.
Boran.
My Bey.
If not by good, then by force.
Tell the Alps to go there.
And let them take the battering
ram and the siege weapons.
Your command, my Bey.
Come on.
My Bey.
Shall we fight Turgut Bey?
We'll fight Turgut Bey first...
But for our calling...
If we have to, we will fight the whole
world as long as our breath suffices.
Come on.
Marmaracık Castle
They will all see.
They will all pay for kidnapping my woman.
Bayındır.
Weigh your words first, then speak.
Alçiçek is not your woman.
It's my daughter.
She was going to be my woman.
We were going to get married.
Will you stand before me now
and defend Osman Bey?
Bayındır Bey.
Bayındır Bey is right, Öktem Bey.
Osman Bey reached the limit by
kidnapping Alçiçek.
It's time to drown them all.
They didn't keep the promise made to me.
You made that promise to me.
They didn't listen to your words.
And now we will not listen to them.
This will not end like this.
Enough, Bengi.
Enough.
Everything that happened
was because of you.
As for you, Bayındır...
I understand you.
You are angry.
I know.
Your pride has been wounded.
However...
Alçiçek is not your woman, she
is my daughter.
I am the one who does
what needs to be done.
Don't ever try to charge
me again, Bayındır.
I wouldn't mind our long
friendship, you know.
You're just pissing us off.
We were disgraced in front of Sultan.
She couldn't stay in the castle
because of her anger.
You, Öktem Bey...
You couldn't keep your daughter.
Bayındır.
Aybars.
Tell Alps to take their swords.
We will go to Yenişehir.
You're not coming, Bayındır.
I'm going to take my daughter.
No work for you there.
Stay safe.
So be it, Öktem Bey.
So be it.
Hüseyin.
I was defeated before
my damned conscience.
That dog, Aktemur.
I should have killed him with my own hands
before handing him over to Olof.
But better late than never.
I'm going to rip that dog's heart
out with my own hands.
Come on.
I thought he left me.
I thought he got scared and ran away.
The truth is that they hurt him a lot.
He was coming.
Otherwise, he would have come.
He would have come.
Are they yours?
They're a gift from Aktemur.
Put them on.
He woke up.
Son.
Thank Allah.
You woke up, right?
Look who we brought to you.
Your uncle kidnapped Alçiçek
from her wedding and brought her to you.
Aktemur.
You are fine, right?
- Mother.
- Yes?
Okay.
You both speak.
I'm at the door.
İnegöl Castle
What are you thinking, Turgut Bey?
Are you afraid
for your property?
We increased the number of Alps.
And the archers were deployed.
All precautions have been taken.
Thank you.
Wherever the Sultan is, the rule
of Beys is abolished.
By increasing these measures...
you're doing unnecessary work, Turgut Bey.
If you knew Osman Bey
as well as I know him...
You would have known that taking
measures is obligatory, Sultan.
I know Osman Bey very well.
But you do not know me.
Archers!
You will definitely take heed.
For where words are not
enough, words are for the sword.
However, I believe that precautions
must be taken despite everything.
If Osman Bey considers his path to be the
right, then he won't listen to anyone.
So, we will speak to him in the
language he understands.
Osman Bey will die at
his slightest mistake.
Let him go ahead and come.
You come with a bang.
No.
My intention is good.
You risked all your possessions and come to
take from Turgut Bey the castle he deserves.
Is this your good intention?
You are right.
This castle belongs to Turgut Bey
as long as he deserves it.
But he doesn't deserve it anymore.
You are going
beyond your limits.
You can't decide that.
I've done a lot of things you said
I couldn't do, İsmihan Sultan.
You will leave the castle now.
The day when I set foot on these
lands, it was over for you.
This is the decision of Sultan Aladdin,
the sole ruler of these lands.
İnegöl Castle was granted to Turgut Bey
by this decree.
Turgut Bey is not only the ruler of
İnegöl...
but also the owner.
İnegöl belongs to me.
Why are you here*
Let justice take its course, Osman Bey.
Sultan.
My brother fell a martyr for these lands.
And I beheaded my greatest
enemy, Nicolas, on these lands.
And I based my dream
many years ago on it.
And I fought for it for many years.
For this reason...
You can't take it from me with
a piece of paper like that.
Do you oppose the Sultan's order?
Like I said...
Neither words nor decisions convinced him.
Soldiers!
Now I ask you again...
Do you oppose the Sultan's order?
Can you risk something like that?
You can't imagine what I would risk.
And you can't expect what I can do.
Don't confuse me with the others.
I am not a Vizier
coming to you with an order.
I am not a Mongol commander.
I am İsmihan Sultan.
Whoever you are...
These lands which I have taken by shedding our blood,
I will not leave without shedding the blood of others.
Is it?
Looks like you're going to lose a lot of things
other than your blood, Osman Bey.
We have a guest now.
Kantakuzenos, the great procurator and
viceroy of the Emperor.
Get away.
Don't make me shed
blood brothers, go away.
Alps!
Lower your weapons.
Alçiçek.
Your mother and and father came, come on.
Come on, Alçiçek.
Bengi Hatun.
You cannot summon
anyone to you like that in my palace.
What does it mean that you kidnapped
my daughter on her wedding day, Malhun Hatun?
What norms do you rule by?
Öktem Bey, you are a reasonable man.
And you know, Osman Bey
can't do that without a reason.
Tell me, Bala Hatun,
is this the way it's done?
My daughter told her mother
that she was going to marry Bayındır Bey.
Is this how you
prevent it, Bala Hatun?
Öktem Bey, someone seems to
have blinded your eyes to the truth.
Aktemur and Alçiçek love each other.
We know the origins, and we have sent
you news and come to your door.
But you broke your promise
and we had to do it.
Do you want your daughter to spend her
life with a man she doesn't love, Öktem Bey?
Come on, put your weapons down
and let's work this out quietly.
We will not listen to
you talk anymore.
Alps, crush whoever stands
in front of you, come on.
My mother.
Alçiçek.
My father.
My daughter
Come on, let's go from here.
Osman Bey, as you can see,
we're here to represent both states.
And your agreement
with us will benefit you.
You didn't look so imposing as you
asking me for help, Kantakuzenos.
It seems that the position
has benefited you a lot.
What happened in the
past happened and ended.
And now I am before you, and
we will make a pact together.
Good.
But we build our future
by looking at our past.
Be careful not to get
this out of your mind.
Now what is this agreement?
Let the Sultan clarify this if she wants.
Here, Konya.
And here, Constantinople.
And you're right in the middle.
That is, we hold the feet of this
table, and you are in the middle of it.
We will now end this situation.
Your presence harms
these lands, Osman Bey.
If you have strength, you have gathered it
from these two countries.
What you did brought nothing but
blood and tears to these lands.
Are you the ones who will secure
reconciliation and peace on these lands?
He only cares about the throne.
And greed for power.
And receiving judgment.
He never helped the people.
All you care about is keeping your places.
It's hyperbole for a man who confiscates the property of
a Bey because he thought differently than he did.
Karacahisar and Kulucahisar.
And even Bilecik Castle.
You will hand these
castles over to me.
All trade documents of these castles will
remain with Byzantium.
And the caravans will operate with
Constantinople.
The same applies to
Söğüt and Yenişehir.
Basically, you will have nothing else left
after signing the agreement.
The lands I took with blood...
You ask me to submit them on paper.
You want me to give you the places that
lie like hammers on the enemy's chest.
And you want me to agree
and be grateful for that.
No.
We have clarified our terms for the
agreement in the best way.
Osman Bey.
10,000 horsemen are
ready to enter Yenişehir.
They are waiting for your decision.
Don't force me to.
A thousand cavalry and 5,000
foot soldiers await my order.
We are here for peace, Osman Bey.
Please, do not shed blood.
I do not wish for bloodshed.
I don't feed on blood.
However...
If you wish to expel me from my country...
Then I will not leave my country
to anyone.
If I'm not there...
This will be the end of your
agreement as well.
I will inform you of my
decision tomorrow.
Alçiçek.
You are fine, right?
If you do something to my daughter!
I will burn you and your palace!
You don't know me and you
haven't seen anything yet.
Aktemur!
I will burn you all!
Watch your words, Hatun.
Who would do anything to Alçiçek?
I got so scared, Aktemur.
I cried a lot.
I thought you left me and
got scared and ran away.
When I was coming to you...
I fell into hell.
That dog Olof said the girl
I love would marry Bayındır.
I didn't believe it.
But you...
You are...
You thought I got scared and
ran away and left you.
You believed everything, however...
You didn't believe my love for you.
Now...
Take off those earrings.
Cry for Bayındır from now on.
Father.
- Let's go from here now.
- Let's go, daughter, let's go.
Come on.
This charade is over.
You've gone too far, however...
You know that my patience is running out.
Come on, let's go.
What's going on, Aktemur*
Where did Alçiçek go?
It's my decision.
I told her to leave.
Osman Bey has kidnapped the girl
from a wedding party held by the Sultan.
And you told her to leave.
Ayşe.
What does this mean, Aktemur?
How did you do this to Alçiçek?
Forgive me for your sake.
I tired you.
However...
I don't trust Alçiçek's love.
She left me in the middle.
Alçiçek that I loved....
She would've done everything she could
and wouldn't have allowed that wedding.
Aktemur.
Do not insist on this matter anymore.
Ayşe.
I called you İltutan. (land-holder)
So that we would hold all lands together.
Near Yenişehir
But now the people of strife unite...
And they want what we have.
Your feet would have trampled
many lands of the infidels.
Now the infidels have united and
want our homeland.
I do not carry this sword in vain.
And I don't make you
wear armor in vain.
This will not be easy.
What is taken by blood
is given by blood only.
Not just our blood...
Rather, they threaten us with the
blood of innocents.
No, we will never give up.
We will never give up.
We will never give up!
Never.
Well, what if...
I'm reluctant to hand it over
so they don't think I'm afraid.
No.
I'm not even afraid of fear.
They can think whatever they wish.
If I don't accept...
Then we will be crushed
between the two states.
The dream of the country we
dreamed of will disappear forever.
However...
If I give the castles...
I will have a chance in
another campaign.
Those who think about their own souls
have been holding back for a while.
As for those who are behind us...
They gave up their lives.
Well, what about...
What if the dreams of those
behind me are shattered?
What will...
What will happen then?
No.
Think, Osman.
Osman.
But I'm at a point where I can't find
a solution through thinking.
No...
My Allah.
My Allah, the owner of everything.
Help this helpless servant of yours.
Ahead is a fire.
A flood is behind us.
Have mercy on me, my Allah.
You are the one who
knows everything.
And you see it all.
My Allah.
Show me the way.
Amin.
There is no word from
Osman Bey yet, however...
we better be careful.
Ayşe.
Are you thinking about what Aktemur did?
He even risked being up against me, Bala.
Despite all your efforts, he says
he doesn't want her.
Actually, I'm thinking about what
we're going to say to Osman Bey
If he doesn't want to,
what will he do, Ayşe?
They shouldn't be unhappy
because we made efforts.
because of Osman Bey.
Let's say
this is good for us.
It's true what you say.
May Osman Bey come safely.
And he brings us good news.
I will talk to him about this in detail.
Inshallah.
Will you allow me?
I brought you news.
But it is not good news.
Kantakuzenos and İsmihan unite.
They both want castles.
What are you saying, Şamil?
What does
Osman Bey say about this?
I don't know.
What do they trust?
They have an army.
They're talking about thousands of
soldiers and cavalry, Malhun Hatun.
Aktemur! Alps!
Aktemur, arm the Alps.
The situation is dangerous.
Thousands of enemy
soldiers will attack us.
Your command.
Not just Alps!
Rather, merchants, students
and everyone else!
Kutlu, go to madrasah quickly!
Your command, my Bey.
Ayşe, go to sisters
and get them ready.
Dursun Fakı, tell all the dervishes
in and around Söğüt and Yenişehir.
We are waiting for him to stand
behind us.
Malhun, are we sure Osman Bey
will make the decision to go to war?
Is the opposite possible, Bala?
We will not hand it over to them.
Osman's work is
incomprehensible to the mind.
We don't want to hand it
over to them, however...
Bala.
Even those we counted
are few in number.
They talk about thousands of soldiers.
Şamil, tell Boran....
to dig trenches near Yenişehir...
and to strengthen the walls.
Let's withdraw the Alps from Söğüt
to this side.
We can't defend Söğüt
while İsmihan is there.
Your command, Malhun Hatun.
Come on, all Alps move!
Bala.
We spent years
fighting back to back.
Do you really give a chance
that we will surrender?
Not surrender, but withdrawal.
We will take back what we gave.
But if we lose our lives by staying
between the two states until then...
There will be nothing left to take.
This property is taken by blood and
given by blood.
That's it.
But even if we back down...
As responsible for the state...
We must take our precautions.
I can't take any chances.
Good.
Mother, I want to go to Karacahisar.
I do not intend to hand over
my trust to anyone.
Send word to Karacahisar...
to double the measures.
You better stay here
until your father comes.
Shall we hand over the castles, mother?
I can't say for sure what
your father's going to do, son.
The enemy cannot be known.
But do not worry.
We have to get through this somehow.
Don't bother.
Okay, mother.
I'll help them with the letters
they'll write to the dervishes.
Dursun Fakı must send them soon.
Well then, come on.
The goal was to have a land since the
era of Süleyman Şah and Ertuğrul Ghazi.
And now all these lands that we got are
being abandoned and retreated, right?
Who said we are retreating?
From whom did you hear it?
Look at this panic.
Who will back down?
You've been this way all these years.
Did you see someone retreat?
If not reverted, then the
headers will disappear.
Will you remain immortal in this world?
The old bull is not afraid of the axe.
My fear is for you.
Never worry for us.
He who was born for war is
not afraid of martyrdom.
We will walk.
It's nice to say, Beys, but...
Look...
How many people are left?
Turgut Bey is not here.
Öktem Bey is not here
Bayındır Bey is not here.
The road exists, but there are
no men left to walk it.
If there is a way to walk, there will be
men walking in it, Emirhan Bey.
Don't you worry.
You can't resist fate, Beys.
We cannot ask
fate for help without making an effort.
Where is Osman Bey, Alps?
Osman Bey is coming.
O Allah.
Come to the court, what
I will say is important.
Söğüt Headquarters
The Sultan doesn't
trust Osman Bey.
If he lines up all these soldiers
and makes Söğüt her headquarters...
She thinks Osman Bey will not
hand over the castles to her.
And what do you think, my Bey?
In your opinion, will he
hand over the castles?
We'll see, Kutan.
We'll see.
Stop, they don't
know what they're doing.
You don't differentiate between
friend and foe yet.
How will you protect me?
How will you fight for me?
You can't even be dogs
in front of my door.
Cut their throats off now.
Till worthy soldiers are found to
stand before my door...
You will stand at my door, Avcı.
Go ahead, Turgut Bey.
The Court opened with the ninety-nine names of Allah,
who made us responsible for the invasion, not the victory.
In the name of Allah the Merciful.
A Bey's court requires more.
Open the doors.
For everyone to hear.
Summon everyone to come.
First, before I speak...
I want to listen to you.
Go ahead.
If you are at war, I am
behind you, Osman Bey.
If you're going to hand over
the castles, I'm behind you too.
This is not the time for opposition.
My Bey.
If we return to our tribes alive as
we went out to offer our souls...
we can't explain ourselves.
Say fight, let's fight.
We suspected you in the past about
who is the right side.
They want the property that was taken
by your sword, Osman Bey.
You are the right side.
We are behind you to death.
I said goodbye to my wife.
I asked permission from my children.
My Alps are ready, I await your orders.
The soul is entrusted to us, Osman Bey.
If this is the time to hand over
that trust... (castle-lands)
We will do that.
My Bey, may Allah
grant us success.
I keep your secrets, my Bey.
I swore to walk with you to the grave.
This is the time.
This is my second life, my Bey.
You gave me the first.
And the second, let it be a sacrifice
for the sake of this cause.
I have nothing to say, my Bey.
You will see me on the battlefield.
As long as brave people
like you are behind me...
As long as knights like
you are on my side...
Nobody can defeat me.
Allah bless you, Mashallah.
And now I will announce my decision.
Osman does not have
enough soldiers and weapons.
Trade routes are under our control.
I mean, he can't come
out in front of us.
If he does...
He knows he will die.
Beys and tribes are attached to me.
Osman is looking for help.
He can't find what he's looking
for, Kantakuzenos.
Osman can't basically lift
all these burdens on his own.
He has no other solution than
to hand over the castles.
What do you think, Turgut Bey?
Will Osman deliver the castles?
Osman Bey, whom I know,
gives his life, his blood, and his head.
But he does not
give his land.
I mean, it won't be that easy.
So, we'll take his soul first.
Then we take the castles.
But I have to see someone first.
You are all wondering what
I am going to say.
But know that my
decision is final.
My properties, Karacahisar...
Kulucahisar...
and Bilecik Castle.
I will hand them over to İsmihan Sultan.
Dissolve all the units that met.
Everyone can return to
their tribes.
- Don't do it, my Bey.
Don't do this.
Until today, you used to
say "your command."
I command...
and you obey.
Send word to İsmihan Sultan.
Envoys will be sent to castles
and fortresses.
Alps will surrender
castles without resistance.
Everyone will come to Yenişehir in batches
without provoking the Sultan.
Your command, my Bey.
The council is over.
Come on.
Osman Bey, you are the Bey of Kayı.
How can you hand over the castles that were
watered with the blood of all those martyrs?
Don't do this, father.
All those Beys are behind you and they
say go ahead.
Why do you stop, father?
My sons.
Everything has its time
And when that time comes, you
will understand me.
I did not expect such a decision
to be issued, Beys.
We risked our lives, but he
didn't, did he, Beys?
Osman Bey was unable to risk his life.
He is only afraid for you, not
for himself.
Do not wrong him.
Is thinking about my
life one of his tasks?
Sultan İsmihan is right
in what she is doing, Beys.
How could he surrender
the castles without bloodshed?
He deserves it.
It's true what you say.
He left us halfway through.
It turns out that Turgut Bey and
those with him chose the right side.
We were mistaken again, Beys.
No sense in wasting time here anymore.
Come on, everyone go to
their tribe.
Oh, Bayındır.
Look at the state you are in.
My Bey.
I have good news for you.
Alçiçek Hatun.
Is this something said publicly?
Speak, let us see, what is this news?
Alçiçek Hatun.
Don't make me lose my mind, talk.
My Bey, Alçiçek Hatun is back home.
When Öktem Bey went to get her, Alçiçek
Hatun was getting ready to go home.
What are you....
What could have happened?
My Bey, I have another news yet.
Could there be a
greater good news than this, Hüseyin?
I heard this from the Beys coming out
of the feast, my Bey.
Osman Bey will give the castles back.
Osman Bey!
You were trying to oppose people.
Now, you will see what will
become of your Beyhood.
As long as you love me, why
don't you talk?
Are you talking to me, Ülgen Hatun?
What? What? No.
Do I know what I'm saying?
Wait.
I will ask you a question.
There is a girl, this girl
is from our tribe.
And this girl has love someone, okay?
This girl heard the young
man talking to himself.
The young man said that he
loved her.
And I told the girl to wait and this guy
will soon confess his love to you.
And did he?
No, he didn't.
He didn't say anything, damn it.
But he's walking around the girl.
But he does not look into her eyes
and tell her that he loves her.
Maybe he's ashamed.
What? Ashamed?
For Allah's sake, why is he even ashamed?
What is the point of being shy?
Can he really be ashamed?
Oh.
May Allah facilitate your work.
You go, do something, look at the shawl.
I was going to east before
my Bey sent me on a mission, but...
Enjoy it.
Did she forgive me?
Ülgen Hatun.
Yes, Cerguday.
Speak up, why are you
ashamed? Come on, speak.
This is not enough for me, will she give
me more food if I ask for it?
I...
I want... to tell you something, however...
Ülgen, girl..
Yes, Cerguday?
Speak.
No, if I ask for more
food, she'll take what I have.
It's enough food, Cerkutay.
No, I wouldn't be able to say that.
He couldn't say two words!
If I wait for him...
He hardly says it while
I'm in my grave!
Oh, my fate!
İsmihan Sultan, my Bey
has accepted the deal.
He'll give the castles to you.
I came to tell you, we're out.
I'm very glad that your Bey
found the right path.
Send him my regards.
This will be good for all of us.
Where did the wrong path lead you?
To me.
You finally picked the right
side, didn't you, Beys?
We have seen the truth, My Sultan,
and here we stand before you.
Shall I punish you for being late?
Or will I reward you for
coming in the end?
Anything that pleases you, my Sultan.
Osman Bey did not give you
your right at any time.
I will prove to you that
I am the right side.
I will give you the property
that I took from him.
Excuse us, my Sultan, we don't deserve it.
Why would I do something unjustly?
I'm not Osman Bey.
Get up.
Uraz Bey, Karacahisar
is yours from now on.
Şahin Bey, Bilecik is yours from now on.
Demirhan Bey, I am sure that you
will rule Kulucahisar with justice.
May it be good.
May Allah grant us to take proper
care of your faithfulness, my Sultan.
May Allah bless you, my Sultan.
May Allah protect you
and the state, my Sultan.
Now go and settle in your castles.
And never forget whose shadow
you're under.
And if you forget, I will become
the sun and burn you.
Salim Bey, you did a good job and
proved your loyalty.
My loyalty is only to you, my Sultan.
They basically pledged
allegiance to you in the arena.
And now it's only official.
If Osman Bey hadn't given up on the castles, their
stubbornness would not have been broken.
This is our strength.
Do not question.
Do you have orders, my sultan?
I want you to know the value of the high position
we conferred on you in Konya, Salem Bey.
I am always at your command, my sultan.
Osman is not someone who abandons
his castles and retreats.
He must have a plan.
Not this time.
Osman was so cornered that
he had no other choice.
Either he would be destroyed
or give up on the castles.
However, I will be prepared
for any move he makes.
And when I find the right opportunity,
I will kill him.
I offer you an endless war, Olof.
You can shed blood until there is no one
left to take revenge on earth.
But you will need soldiers
and weapons for that.
I'm now empowered
to provide this for you, you know that.
I know.
That is why I am with you in this war.
In order to shed the blood of Muslims...
...I decided to be a Christian.
Your true birth will be after you get to
know Jesus Christ, Olof.
I knew you would find the right way.
For this reason, I brought
the priest with me.
Olof.
You buried your previous life by baptizing.
And you have been
resurrected to your new life.
May Jesus Christ bless you
Life is strange.
When I started my day,
my god was Odin.
Now I will breathe for the sake of the
Father and the Son and the Holy Spirit.
Our bonds have become very strong.
We will expel the Muslims from
these lands together.
Can I come in my Bey?
Come in.
Sir, we have handed over the castles to the gentlemen
We sacrificed our blood to have these castles
.” (Karacahisar Castle
Not only that, but we gave our lives
We can't give up
Ismahan thinks she has put
her loyal masters on those thrones
But it was I who sent the gentlemen for her
(Kolugahisar Castle)
I told a game within a game
And (Ismahan) swallowed this bait
Bilecik Castle
The ones whose heart beat for war
won't accept whatever you offer.
You cannot deceive the ones whose
heart beat for the name of Allah.
Beys who seemed loyal to Ismihan...
...are actually loyal to us and our case.
They are happy because they think...
...they captured the castles and
assigned their men there.
Castles are still Turks' home.
Whatever the enemy does...
...as long as my Beys are there...
...the authority is ours.
Ismihan Sultan
will not have enough.
She will set her eyes on Yenisehir
Certainly.
She have turned the palace upside down
This was not enough for her and now
she is setting her eyes on our lands.
We know how to scratch those eye out.
Everything has a time.
They made their move.
Now they think they have won.
But we had already made our move.
And with Allah's permission...
We will be victorious, Inshallah.
- Inshallah.
- Inshallah my Bey.
What has to happen will happen.
Come on, alps.
Marmaracik Castle.
Alcicek.
Alps!
Clear the yard.
Are you still crying over
Subasi?
You disgraced us to everyone
in your wedding.
Wasn't that enough, daughter?
Who am I talking to?
Who am I talking to, Alcicek?
Is this how you keep your promise?
Hatun!
Enough already.
- Cut her some slack.
- Oktem Bey!
This is not the right time
to talk about it!
We are even late!
The reason behind her walking all over us
is obvious!
Look at my face!
Mother!
Would you like to see the grave you
placed your daughter in?
Look and see.
Enjoy watching your daughter's funeral!
But know this...
...you are the reason
behind everything happened yesterday.
Bengu!
Let her!
Let her, father!
Let her hit me.
But a slap won't be enough for her.
I should die.
I should die so that we both find peace.
If this doesn't satisfy you...
...hold the dagger you!
This must be the only way you relieve!
I died the day you tricked me to
go back and give up on Aktemur, mother!
Kill me again, mother!
Kill me!
Bengi!
Don't you dare!
Oktem Bey!
Never raise your hand to me again...
...just because I did
what you couldn't do.
Or you will regret it because
you have no idea what I would do.
It's enough.
Enough.
Oktem Bey!
Bayindir Bey is coming!
Let him.
Stand up, daughter.
No bird will fly!
I don't want a mistake!
Your command, my Bey!
Aktemur!
Good for you.
You have boosted the precautions.
However, you tire yoursel up too much.
Get some rest.
How am I going to rest, mother?
It's my job.
I neglected it for a long time
for no reason. It's enough.
What do you mean for no reason?
What do you mean by that, Aktemur?
Didn't you fight me
all this time for that girl?
Didn't you say you fell in love?
All the obstacles are removed,
your uncle asked for the girl.
What happened now?
Have you lost you interest?
Mother!
Alcicek is the one...
...who gave up on me in the first problem.
She didn't believe in my love.
- But son...
- There is no but mother.
While I was fighting for my life for her...
She was making her dowery ready
for Bayindir.
It's over.
Alcicek issue is done.
Alps!
Bring the gift boxes
of Bayindir Bey.
What does this mean, Oktem Bey?
I did not back out of this...
...because of Osman's reckless behaviour.
I still want Alcicek.
Don't, Bayindir.
Don't.
Doesn't matter if you still want her.
I changed my mind.
I will not give my daughter to you.
What are you saying, Oktem Bey?
Bengi Hatun.
Do you have something to say?
Bayindir Bey.
Everything is still fresh.
Allow us to think for a while.
There is nothing to think about.
You shall consider Alcicek
as your sister, Bayindir Bey.
This wedding is not based on
our desires, Oktem Bey.
I've considered Alcicek as a sister
for years.
This is Ismihan Sultan's order.
This is why we are here.
We know this.
Bayindir Bey, we know it.
But he is a father, you know.
Such an event shall not be decided in haste.
Right, Oktem Bey?
I said what I had to say.
Let alone Ismihan Sultan...
...even if the Caliph was here...
I wouldn't give my daughter.
The good visit is the short visit, Bayindir.
Take your gifts and go on your way.
And if Ismihan Sultan feels upset...
...tell her what I said to you exactly.
Bayindir.
Good.
Whatever you say.
So be it.
Huseyin!
Alps.
Thank you, father.
I would die
if you gave me to him.
I never want to hear such words.
Agreed?
From now on,
I won't do anything without your knowledge
How is Osman now, Avci?
He was crushed under your power,
my Sultan.
He must be perished.
I have taken his castles and cut his breath.
And when the time comes...
....I will cut out his liver.
But...
Osman...
He is injured.
He won't stop.
Send a messenger to Turgut.
Let him come to me immediately.
Avci.
You will send a messenger to
one more person as well.
Ismihan Sultan thinks that...
...I'll hand the rights of all those
martyrs and Ghazis...
...to her without fighting.
Her thoughts will be her end.
Everything has a date.
When the time comes...
...as it happens to every hypocrite...
...the chain of truth will bring
her death.
You have a lot of responsbility to take
in this way of truth, Beys.
Your command, Osman Bey.
Uraz Bey.
The weakest point of Karacahisar Castle...
...are the blind spots of walls.
Enhance them like gates.
Emirhan Bey.
The weakest point of
Kulucahisar is...
...the east gates.
Fix them.
Eyvallah(Yes) my Bey.
Sahin Bey.
Bilecik's weakest point is...
...the north enterance
Triple the number of archers there.
As you command, my Bey.
You won't make a move
without informing me.
Eyvallah my Bey.
Do not go easy on supplies.
Because Ismihan Sultan
will cover the expenses.
Distribute gold to our people abundandtly.
She will throw a sprat to catch a mackere.
As you say, my Bey.
Let's go then.
May our conquest be blessed.
Eyvallah.
Sogut.
Which guest of yours are we waiting for...
...Hadrat Sultan?
Is it Osman Bey again?
Are we waiting for him?
You are going to be more pissed off...
...than seeing Osman Bey, Turgut Bey.
Sit down, sit down, Turgut Bey.
We are not used to recieving respect.
Sit down.
No.
No, this won't work.
I cannot accept this.
In my presence.
And without my permission.
If you have one more move...
...you will both lose you heads.
With this ignoble...
Instead of eating at the same table...
Better cut off my head!
Come to your senses, Turgut Bey.
Olof is a Byzantine general under
Kantakuzenos' command.
Like you being a commander under me.
I demand to be removed from my position!
Your demand has been rejected, Turgut Bey!
So kill me and finish this!
We don't have to do that.
Because you are an intelligent man, who can
forget the past and look to the future.
Mongols have destroyed everywhere!
The people do not need war, but peace.
And for that, we must unite.
From now on, we'll move together.
Osman won't stop.
Turgut Bey.
Olof has put his men in castles.
Because the Beys we put in castles...
...are still loyal to Osman
He is going after his case.
This is what Osman Bey needs to do.
Osman won't stop.
He won't.
If we are to form a union...
...we have to unite.
I expect you to calm down and adapt.
Turgut Bey.
Calm down...
...and adapt.
Are you still alive, Sarkis?
Who knows in what disguise
we'll see you next.
Don't question the loyalty of my men, Olof.
Or I will question your loyalty to
Kantakuzenos...
...because you couldn't get the lands
you wanted from him and asked me.
So what you are saying is...
...that the reason behind we collaborate
with him...
...is that Osman Bey still
rules the castles.
Yenisehir Osman Bey's Palace.
There we are.
This is the hardest part of the meat.
Hard to cook, hard to eat.
Just like the Beys who leave.
Cerkutay.
Chop them up for the soup.
As you command my Bey.
O Allah.
Do not eat it.
It's for the soup.
Do you think I am a savage
to eat raw meat?
You don't understand the taste.
In Osman Bey's kitchen,
alps should not talk too much.
Don't babble.
Boran, chop the onions up.
Make them thin enough
not to feel them while chewing.
Your command, my Bey.
I will cut them as thin as
I strike the infidels in their foreheads.
What is there?
Why do the Beys stand idly?
Is it because they are Beys
who don't want to get their hands dirty?
Come on, we've got a lot of work to do,
the meat takes a long time.
Check out the dough and the bread .
We will prepare food for all those people
- Aykut brother.
- Yes brother.
Let's call Beys on the dough
so that we can work on the meat.
Yes, you are right, my brother.
My Bey, come sit here.
I can see what you are doing.
You are trying to keep me busy
with the dough, right?
- Aktemur.
- My Bey.
Come here will you?
Come here, come.
Take this meat.
Take this too.
Separate the nerves from the meat.
Thinly my Bey said.
Praise be!
We thought your skills are limited
with the swords, Osman Bey.
You are also skillful in the kitchen!
I don't like to talk about my skills.
Now that we know you are a chief...
We hope to see you valiants
in the kitchen more.
Thank you, Hatuns, thank you.
- Good luck with it.
- Thank you.
While you think you are doing
something good...
...ladies crack jokes on your head.
Never forget this, Aktemur.
Cerkutay, why are you waiting?
- We are cooking for many!
- Yes my Bey.
Chop it thinly.
Look at Cerkutay.
He can't do anything.
He wasted it.
And they still give him double swords.
If I had known today was his rest day,
I would have cooked for Cerkutay.
I would have cooked very well.
I always do it when he is hungry though.
So tell me.
Why did you reject Alcicek?
Expectations, uncle.
She thought I would marry someone else.
But it was impossible for me
to marry someone else.
But she made it possible.
She lost me.
Let your heart guide you.
Bring the heart, Baysungur.
Cook it and let it spread joy on our table.
- Is the soup ready, Gurbuz?
- Soon to be, my Bey.
Olof's men have received
the castles from the Beys.
No bird will fly there
without our knowledge.
Strengthen the blind spots of the walls.
Send the blacksmiths there immediately.
- Increase the number of men on walls.
- Yes my Bey.
We have an agreement with Ismihan Sultan.
We will rule Karacahisar together
from now on, Uraz Bey.
I hope the best.
Yes.
We'll rule Bilecik together from now on.
Hope for the best.
The orders of the mother sultan are
upon us.
We'll be loyal to the agreement.
We'll rule Kulucahisar together.
Beys.
Osman wanted to sabotage our campaign.
And we prevented this thanks to Olof
We have only one condition
for this friendship.
The innocents will never be harmed,
will they, Olof?
I will protect the innocent
for as long as I live.
I swear on God and his son Jesus.
Are you satisfied now, Turgut Bey?
Would you still like to leave our table?
If Osman Bey's ruling is to
end over the castles...
...I am satisfied, Hadrat Mother Sultan.
So go ahead.
Don't count too much on
this Konur, standing next to you
He is the eye and ear of Osman Bey.
Praise be to Allah, Lord of the Worlds, who
seated us at this table safe and sound...
...and bestowed upon us many blessings.
- Amen.
I thank Allah, my Lord, for being here
with my family, brothers and tribe.
Amen.
- Amen.
Come on then, in the name of Allah,
the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful
Thank you, Beys.
You turned the kitchen into a battlefield.
However, the food is delicious.
No, Alps will work together
and clean it, right?
- You will clean the kitchen right?
- Of course, your command.
Yes they will clean it.
Thank you valiants.
We expect the same in your own homes
in the future.
Do it also without a Bey's command.
They burned the meat and bulgur.
Don't let these people into the kitchen
again, Osman Bey.
What are you saying, Ulgen?
What can I say, my Bey?
I am saying that...
...our kitchen is too small for
this many people.
Should we have set the table outside?
The food gets delicious where it is cooked.
Here is good.
Can I come in my Bey?
Come.
There is news from the castles, my Bey.
Eyvallah, we'll talk,
sit down and eat something first.
They set a trap, my Bey.
Olof and his men settled in the castles.
Who is behind this?
Ismihan Sultan and Kantakuzenos.
They ordered shared ruling.
Clear my way!
Someday
when all this is over...
...I hope you won't bring Olof
at Inegol throne.
I don't trust them, Turgut Bey.
I trust you completely.
Confidence comes on top of everything.
One spark would be enough
to start a huge fire.
I am responsible for
extinguishing these sparks.
Just like how I deposed Mesut and enthroned
my son in order to revive the Seljuk dynasty...
I will depose Osman too.
You killed him, right?
We should be afraid of you,
Mother Sultan.
My son, the great Sultan, was merciful
and allowed him to live.
He is now a prisoner in his palace,
which he loved so much.
Praise be!
Inegol Castle.
What are you doing, Turgut?
After all this happened...
Who are you sitting with?
The wound caused by your brother makes you
sit with the enemy at the same table!
But where does this road lead?
What am I going to do?
What do you think you will do, Turgut Bey?
How long have you been here?
Welcome, I didn't notice you.
Welcome.
If you don't want to hear, you don't hear.
If you don't want to see, you don't see.
What is it?
The property you acquired...
The property which is your right...
Does it overwhelm you now?
I see that you will give advice again.
Why have you come, Kumral Abdal?
I came to see
if you pulled yourself together.
Why are we in this situation, Kumral Abdal?
You come and wound my heart constantly.
Have you ever gone to Osman Bey
and asked him?
Why are you in this situation?
Do you think he pulled himself together?
Or are your advices only to me?
O great world!
O high throne!
Men who wanted to spit
in each other's faces gathered together...
...while friends clash.
But no, you are not the only guilty
here, world.
Guilt is also yours, you ventured into
alliance with the enemy to punish your brother.
You are also guilty, who cooperate with the
enemy and throw your brother under the bus.
Kumral Abdal.
Your words are sharper than
the sword and cauterize the heart
But I will not lose my respect for you.
Get out of my way for now.
I, I will not listen to you.
Do not listen to me, Turgut Bey!
Who am I?
Your heart will show you the truth.
Your inner voice will convince you to
wear the dress of love.
Forget about me.
Silence your soul so that you can
hear yourself.
Later.
Come on, valiant.
- My Bey.
- Tell me.
What is this demon Hatun after?
They've got Olof's men stationed
in the castles, my Bey.
I know this.
Anything other than that?
What she did terrifies even the devil
Sultan Ismahan made Olof and Turgut Bey
sit at the same table.
Turgut.
How did your eyes become so blind that
you cooperate with the infidels?
How?
They claim that they united
for the sake of the stolen lands.
But they divide the unity that
we have established to be strong.
It all happened after
she enthroned her son.
Well, what about Sultan Masud?
Is there news about him?
Yes.
Ismihan Sultan keeps him in the palace.
Nice
We'll go to Konya then.
If we save Sultan Mesut, he will keep
Ismihan and Aladdin away from us.
God willing, we will
also pay this calamity for us, sir
They are here, my Bey.
You have another mission now.
You will go to Yenişehir.
Ismihan Sultan is going crazy.
Inform Malhun Hatun.
They shall take precautions against
Ismihan Sultan.
- As you command, my Bey.
- Eyvallah.
We will ruin their plans.
Ah Osman Bey.
You tell me I am selfish
but you don't leave your selfishness!
You backdoor us.
Ah brother, ah!
Come on.
Sogut.
You aree coming
from Constantinople, right?
There must be marvelously huge palaces.
Best of all, madam.
You will use your skills for me very soon.
My Sultan, there is news from Turgut Bey.
Konur and Osman Bey met.
Osman Bey is going to Konya
with his alps.
Send letter to Osman's palace.
I will visit them.
Marta.
Let's see that palace
before owning it.
Avci, wait.
Right now...
...you'll first...
Yenisehir Osman's Palace
Here, here!
Don't miss anything.
Ismihan Sultan is very noble.
She may not like the food.
Let's not give her any excuse.
Who doesn't like your food?
Was it you, Cerkutay?
Leave!
Who knows what she will find to criticize!
Get up, get up, get up!
Get up, come on!
- No one will realise one bite.
- No way, no!
No, go, leave!
But, Cerkutay...
I keep your share in the kitchen.
- Ulgen Hatun.
- You'll like it.
Hey! He did it again!
Damn!
I said his share is in the kitchen,
what more do you want?
Welcome.
This coming- is never a
good sign, however...
Our table is like a home for those
who come to us as a friend...
and our sword is sharp against those
who come to us as an enemy.
It is, however...
İsmihan Sultan, did she come alone?
İsmihan Sultan has come.
Attention everyone! Mother İsmihan Sultan!
Welcome.
Alps, we're going to Konya, come on.
Your command, my Bey.
Come on.
Tell me.
The thousand cavalry sent by Kazan
are on their way, Commander Samagar.
Cavalries!
They did not trample
these lands sufficiently.
Get your men ready, Konya Palace
will soon belong to its real owner.
These thousand knights will make
Samagar more powerful.
Commander Samagar, there is
news from İsmihan Sultan.
Osman, bey of Kayı tribe, is coming to Konya.
Prepare for him a proper reception, Samagar.
Osman, killing you is
written in my destiny.
Let him come.
Death will embrace him.
What do you think, Marta?
Can you turn
this old inn into a mansion?
It suffices to command
me to do so, my Sultan.
Enjoy it.
What is this?
How do you put
that in front of me?
You stupid.
- What did I do?
- Shut up!
Get out of here!
İsmihan Sultan.
What you are doing is wrong.
What did you find
wrong with this food?
Shame?
I am the Mother Sultan of Seljuqs.
How do you put food
like that in front of me?
You obviously have bad
taste, İsmihan Sultan.
There is no other reason
to fault this food.
Hatun, you have forgotten who the
woman in front of you is.
The price will be heavy if you want
to remember who I am.
We have a reputation of making others pay,
not our own, İsmihan Sultan.
What you did with that food is
disrespectful.
Don't.
After all, this food is man-made and
there may be something missing in it.
But we do not want this
matter to spoil our assembly.
You are right, Ayşe Hatun.
For your sake...
I will ignore this.
My Sultan, come to our inn tomorrow
and I will prepare a table for you.
Oh, Bengi Hatun.
The position you are in
here does not suit you
Your place is in Konya.
And I saw your skill on the wedding day.
But, of course, we experienced
some inconveniences.
Right, Hatuns?
If I had sat at this table...
This is for your own sake, my Sultan.
This Kayiı tribe has dishonored me
in front of all the Turkmens.
And now, they're talking bad about
my daughter.
Know your limit, Hatun.
You did what you did on your own.
- If you weren't the reason they...
- Me?
I am thinking about my daughter's future.
Bala Hatun, you kidnapped
my daughter on her wedding night.
Now, you are slandering her
like that was not enough, Malhun Hatun!
You don't think about
your daughter's future or anything!
If that were the case, you would have
opposed her marriage with Bayındır!
Shut up!
That is enough!
Konya Seljuq Palace
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
We want to meet Sultan Aladdin.
Watch out, brother.
This is the horse Sultan Aladdin
gifted to him.
Do not look at the truth
with suspicion, soldier.
Otherwise, I will blind your eyes.
I am the former judge of Konya,
Dursun Fikih.
And this is Osman Bey's son Aladdin Bey.
Do not let us use force.
Dursun Fikih, forgive us.
Welcome.
This way.
Come on, my Bey.
Dursun Fikih, you know the rules.
You cannot enter without
delivering your weapons.
Watch your words brother.
An alp never drops his weapon.
We cannot hand you our weapons.
We will abide by the rules.
This way my Bey.
We are behind you my Bey.
Hadrat Sultan.
Sultan Mesut.
Insolence runs in your veins!
I came here to teach you.
The appropriate thing to do is
that you visit Bengi Hatun.
However, she acted maturely
and came here with me.
Now you will apologize to
Bengi Hatun for what you have done.
Ismihan Sultan.
Do you hear what you're saying?
We didn't do wrong to anyone.
We went and asked for the girl
according to the tradition.
We kidnapped Alcicek so as not to
let her marry a man she doesn't love.
You are right.
You are right, Ayse Hatun.
You kidnapped the girl.
Instead of having a wedding and
taking her as your daughter-in-law...
you sent the girl back to
her father's house
Everyone is talking about this now.
This is the matter of a young lady!
This is no game!
Don't let me repeat myself and apologize!
We will not apologize to anyone,
Ismihan Sultan.
Your disrespect towards us is enough!
If you are a friend then eat your food
and thank us, then get up and go!
And if you are an enemy, then stop this
nonsense, draw your sword and face us!
Who do you think you are to
dismiss me from my property?
You will pack up and go back to your tents!
The palace is not for you!
From now on, this palace will be mine.
Marta!
You will turn this dump into a palace!
Whatever you say, my Sultan.
Have you set your eyes on the palace now?
Your visit shall end!
- Enough of you!
- Bala!
Bala!
Calm down Bala.
You limitless!
Mother Selcan used to say,
"Only a fool guest tries to host the real owner"
You think you own the property
and we are the guests.
Only our swords will talk now!
- Let go of me!
- Bala!
Here is your end, Osman!
Killing you is written in my destiny.
My end will not be at your hands.
- Where is Sultan Mesut?
- He has never been here.
This is not Mesut's, but your grave.
You!
You traitor!
Yes Osman Bey.
It's time for you to pay for
all the injustice you've done!
Are you the one
who will make me pay the price?
After you get the biggest hit
from those you underestimated...
...you won't be able to talk
like that again.
Wait!
He is our prey.
Attack!
After killing you,
your land will be under our rule.
I will descend upon
your country like black clouds!
I'll break your hand if you touch my ring!
The noose will be wrapped around your neck
Even if the noose wraps my neck,
I'm still a wolf!
But you...
You are only foxes even when you die.
Once I get up...
...I will make you all pay.
Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries